Thank you for them.
>> How does it feel to get How does it feel
to get it done?
>> It feels amazing. Uh this whole day is
kind of surreal. I'll never forget this
day, but this is a day that, you know, I
kind of worked for my whole life. Um I
wor I I knew I was going to be here. I
didn't know when. I didn't know how. I
didn't know what the outcome was going
to be, but I'm here. And so I just, you
know, want to say thank you to everybody
that played a part to making it happen.
But for me, um it means everything. It
means a whole lot that just this
organization believes in me and I'm
going continue to keep giving them
everything that I have in my soul to
make sure that they know that.
>> You told us on day one that you had the
faith that this was all going to get
done. What brought you to that point?
>> Just the Lord. Just knowing that my
whole life has been ups and downs.
There's been es and flows. There's been
uh things where I didn't think I would
come out of, but you know, the great
Lord brought me out of. And so, this is
this was nothing else. This is nothing
else different. You know, this is
something I knew was going to happen.
Like I said, I just didn't know when. Um
I expected it to happen. The work that I
put in my whole life was was up until
this moment, and I'm going continue to
keep working. But um for me, it's just a
blessing just to be here, honestly.
>> I know you're still I know you're still
processing probably all of this, but um
to be able to share this
>> and to be able to make that call,
what was that like for you? And it kind
of hit you in waves?
>> Yeah. Uh I'll tell you, it was a it was
a whole bunch of tears. I'd say it was a
tears of joy. tears of and just tears of
just emotion and just like saying like
like finally like I just just it was a
sigh of relief. You know when I called
my mom she just said I can't stop crying
and made my eyes ball because I I I can
feel it. I can feel it through the
phone. I felt how she felt cuz I know
exactly how she's feeling. She knows how
I feel. So again it's just something
that we've all worked for so hard my
whole life. Um and to be able to say
it's finally here is it's very surreal
but it's al always a blessing. What
about the phone call this morning when
you got the news from your agent? What
was that like for you personally?
>> Uh, it was everything. So, I kind of
knew today might have been a day. Um, we
we planned this meeting a couple days
ago that we're going to meet with Sean
and, um, Matthew Shearan this morning
and, uh, at Coach Mety's office. And so,
um, just going in there with initial
meetings. Um, we gave him we gave him
the offer. We gave him the things that
we wanted. Um, and you know, the great
the great Rams organization and you
know, Matthew and Coach McVey, they
discussed and they came back to me and
man, I couldn't believe what they said.
I honestly I didn't wasn't expecting
them to say yes. But when they did, I
you should have seen me in the room. I
said,
dropped my hands in my my face and I
just started thanking the Lord because
man, it was it was a feeling I'll never
forget. It's kind of like a draft day
feeling and then this type of feeling. I
don't know which one's better, but
they're both up there for sure.
>> To get it done with the Rams?
>> Oh, it means everything. Um, for me, I'm
all about commitment. You know, I'm all
about the loyalty. The people that, you
know, pour into me, I'm going to pour
into you. And the Rams have done nothing
but that since I've gotten here, since,
you know, I arrived in 2022, um, through
all the difficulties that I've had in my
journey of injuries and whatnot. And
they never really bad eye. You know,
Coach McVey has always been there for me
since day one. He's always instilled
that confidence in me that, you know, I
was going to continue to be the player
that, you know, I hope to be. And he's
done that since, like I said, since I
broke my foot. I remember him texting me
in that hotel room um telling me that
you know it's I'm going to be okay and
I'm going to be better and I just
remember sitting in that bed and again I
started crying because like this means
so much so much to me and you know for
my coach to come out and text me when
and you know when I was at my roughest
times in my rookie year it meant so much
to me. So um just knowing that you know
that the organization is with me is
everything.
>> That's why you can tell that Sean takes
your journey so personally that he fuels
him in some ways too. that mutual energy
that you guys have
>> for him to be in the room to be part of
telling you
>> this is happening for you. What was that
like? And can you kind of take us
through the moment?
>> Yeah, I mean it was everything. Like I
said, just
>> being able to have a coach like that.
I've never had I mean I've had high
school coaches like that, but I I
haven't had a coach that really really
connected to me on a on a real level.
You know, Coach McVey, he like I said,
he's more worried about me as a human
being than I am a player. Um, and so
just being able to, you know, have him
in those negotiations throughout the
whole time is just to me it showed me
that, you know, my coach cares about me.
You know, my coach really wants me to
see the best for me and he knows and he
thinks that I deserve the best. And so,
um, just being in that meeting room with
him, being able to explain to him how I
felt about where I was coming from and
just why I felt like I deserve the
things that I, you know, I I work for.
Um, it was everything just to be able to
allow him to hear that and see the true
emotion of what it meant.
>> Couple more.
>> So important to you to show up for
training camp.
Um, I don't want to say it wasn't for
the money. It was nothing for that. It
was just for me personally to show them
like I'm always continue to be the same
guy I always have. Nothing's ever going
to change me. I'm not going to let the
business of this world. I I explained
this later. I explained this one time in
my interview. I'm not going to let the
business um affect my or the pleasure
affect my business. You know, this is
where I come and be who I am. This is
where I get I get to escape the world.
This is where, you know, I can truly be
just present where my feet are at in
this on this field. So, I didn't want to
take that away from me. Um, for me it
was football. I love football. This is
what I'm about. This is all I do. So, it
wasn't a business strategy for me to,
you know, not hold out or not show up.
For me, it was more like, man, my
teammates need me and I need this for
myself. And so, why would I do that? Why
would I, you know, hurt myself in a in a
way kind of
>> that relationship that you have with
coach where he treats you like a person,
not a player, is that why you felt
confident just coming to camp and not
wanting to hold out because of that
relationship with coach? Yeah, I knew
what I knew what I know what the Rams
are are about and I know what we stand
for and I know the standard here uh is
not that. You know, I don't I know a
person who thinks that they're bigger
than the program is not where we're at.
And so, uh for me, I didn't want to give
off any type of ill feeling to my
teammates, to the organization, to
myself. Like I said, um for me, it was
just showing up and being present,
continuing to be the man that, you know,
I aspire to be, continuing to keep being
the athlete that I aspire to be, the
teammate, the brother, um everything in
my life. It was just continuing to get
better. And um the only way I knew how
to do that was be around the people that
love me and uh be around the people that
I love. And so uh for me it was like why
wouldn't you show up? You know this is
what you do. And so man I it's just a
blessing. I'm so lost to words at times
and I can't really understand it. I
can't wait to call my mom again to make
sure that it's real and to make sure
that you know we all you know the hard
work is finally you know it's paying
off. And so we're I'm going to continue
to keep working the way that I know how
to and I'm going continue to keep going.
You know that's all I know.
>> All right guys.
>> Appreciate you guys so much.
You know,
>> you can go over.
>> I'm gonna have to reach over.
Um, you know, good day of work today.
You know, we, you know, I was kind of
bouncing around back and forth, but
there was a lot of good things. I think
ultimately, credit to coach
Shottenheimimer and, uh, and the
Cowboys, you know, they're a great host
today. Um, and this is an opportunity
for us to take a step in the right
direction. Also, I think it was really
special for Kairen. Um, you know, great
representation of a guy that, you know,
represents and epitomizes everything
that we want to be about. um the
approach that he took and you know give
a ton of credit to Drew Rosenhouse. Uh
Matthew Sharon really led the way for
us. But uh being able to sit down with
Matthew and myself and then Drew and
Kiran this morning, I think the coolest
thing where you know this is the right
thing is obviously for him number one
and um how important it was for him and
his family and how he wanted to still be
here. But then when you start to see his
teammates reactions, um, you know, we
always talk about enjoyment and
enjoyment for other successes. And when
you see how happy authentically his
coaches, his teammates are for him, um,
you feel really good for him. And, and
the best part about it is is he'll just
continue to do what he's done. You know,
he's like, I can't wait to work even
harder. And it's like, I don't think you
can work any harder, man. You just keep
approaching it the way that you are. And
today was a good day for the Rams. I
think we came out of it clean, which is
important. And so, uh, you know, we'll
look at the tape and like anything else,
you know, good or bad, you know, we'll
move forward and we'll learn from it
and, uh, you know, continue to try to
stack days.
>> On Kron, he mentioned that having a
meeting scheduled with you and Drew and
his mother this morning and that, um, I
don't know how often you get to deliver
news like that to a player in person,
but what was that like for you?
>> It was really finalizing. You know,
there were still some things that we had
to work through, Stu. Um, you know, they
were they were great people to be able
to work with. You know, I think these
things can be challenging and can be
emotional and there's a lot of things
that are involved in this, but it never
got that way. It was always very
collaborative. I think there was great
communication throughout and I think
that's a credit to both sides. And so it
was awesome, Stu. Um, you know, and I
think, you know, one of the things
that's important is is continue to try
to be able to, you know, lean into these
conversations, be there for guys, but
also, you know, be able to provide some
of the understanding from both ends and,
uh, approach these with empathy and
understanding. And and I'm glad that we
were able to finish it.
I'll come to you right after you treat
him more like a person than a player.
How does that make you feel as a coach
when you hear him sort of attribute why
he's happy to be here?
>> That's everything, you know. I I'm I
really appreciate that, you know,
because um you know, there's some been
some different times where you know, you
maybe haven't been that when you want to
be that and um you know, and that's
important and and and I love him. He's
been one of those guys. I've mentioned
different players before that are secure
enough in themselves to challenge you
because they love you and care about you
and he knows I feel the same and he's an
easy guy to root for. So, I appreciate
you telling me that. That sure means a
lot to me.
>> Guys, we'll get a couple more.
>> What's that?
>> Good. Good. Yeah, he's he's making good
progress. He feels good. We've been able
to kind of increase some things behind
the scenes and so he's in good spirits.
You know, he Reggie and I sat down and
we have a good plan, which I'm not going
to get specific with you guys about. Um,
but we do have a good plan in place that
uh that we feel good about and he's he's
progressing in the right direction.
>> Go ahead.
>> Kar's the first running back running
back to get a contract extension to Todd
Burley. What makes him different than
some of the other backs that have been
productive?
>> You know, I I don't know that you want
to compare him to anybody else. We've
been really fortunate to have a lot of
special people in our building.
Obviously, Todd made a tremendous impact
on our football team, but I think this
represents not exclusive to the running
back position, but a human being that's
handled everything the right way. He's
shown the mental and physical toughness
that we're looking for. Um the way that
he responds to to both the good things
with humility and some of the
challenging setbacks with the growth
mindset that we're looking for. He's a
great teammate. He's got great energy.
And so, you know, this was something
that was earned. You know, he earned
this. He's been a really impactful
teammate and and person and player for
us. And so, I'm really happy for him.
And uh and he deserves this.
>> And we gonna get Kurt, Jordan, and then
Maria. Got to go. seen uh Devonte Adams
today against a team other than
yourself. How would you evaluate his
performance?
>> What did you think?
>> 17 play.
>> Yeah, I think so, too. He he was uh he
was outstanding, but he's been
outstanding from the jump. Um you know,
he's just got this great demeanor, you
know, and this isn't a game, but you
know, it's ramped up a little bit when
you practice against somebody else. And
I remember when we've been on the other
side of these practices and you're kind
of looking like, oh, he's fun to watch.
And so, um he had great command today. I
thought Jimmy was awesome. You know,
Jimmy did a great job. U ball didn't
touch the ground much for him, but
Devonte was uh Devonte was what he's
been. Uh and that's consistent. He's
elevating people. He made his plays and
and he's a he's a stud. He's special.
>> Sean, um no, you're not a doctor. Yes.
But just um at the beginning of this
sort of separate situation, we talked
about how it's something he's dealt with
before. He knows how to deal with it,
knows how to handle. Just to clarify, is
it at all related to he went through
something scary a couple years ago after
that New Orleans game with
>> Oh, no, no, no. It doesn't have anything
that that was more of No, that that's a
separate deal. So, it's it's totally
different and I know you kind of
understand the history of all that. And
so, what I what I had said was, you
know, there's been some different things
that he's worked through as it relates
to his back, whether it's in Detroit or
even at different times here where
there's been some things that, you know,
flare up. And so we are airing on the
side of caution and you know you guys
will have more of an understanding of
what's going on as time goes and um you
know you'll talk to him and and then I
think you know ultimately it's it's
about being smart and safe and getting
him back out there with a plan that uh
people that are experts have kind of
advised us on what's the best thing and
um and so for that I'll defer to them on
that stuff. wrap up with you, Maria.
>> Sean, every player has the right to deal
with their contract in their own way,
but talk about his integrity of being
out here every day practicing and making
sure he was part of his team.
>> Yeah, I think the first thing he said is
everybody approaches these things
differently. And so, um, what I am
appreciative of just from my vantage
point is that he came, um, I think he
had a lot of trust in Drew, a lot of
trust in, you know, the way that things
were going behind the scenes and and he
focused on what he could control. Um,
and did that make it, you know, more
likely for us to want to work in good
faith with him? Yeah, of course. But
that doesn't mean if we have a situation
in the future where somebody does decide
to hold out that that's like the end-
all beall. But, um, I think what you're
getting at is we're very grateful. It's
it's a, you know, and that's a tribute
to who he is. You guys know what he's
about. I don't think we were at all
surprised, but when you do go through
these different circumstances, people
confirm what you had hoped uh, you had
always felt about him. And that's all he
continues to do is is confirm why he's a
special and a rare human.
>> Okay, thank you guys.